9japredict.com 2010-11-10

# Welcome to NAIJA PREDICT

9JAPREDICT.COM PRIVACY POLICY

Introduction  
9japredict wants visitors to its website to know that we are just as concerned as you are about the privacy of any personal information that you may choose to provide us ("Personal Information"). In this respect we have invested heavily in providing a world class Information Security Management System.

Personal Information is any information about you and may include your name and address, date of birth, payment card details, details of predicting transactions and account transfers and any other information you may wish to provide. 9jaPredict is endeavouring to ensure that our business practices that involve the use of your Personal Information are compliant with privacy regulations in the countries where we operate. Accordingly, in this policy document (the ?Privacy Policy?), 9jaPredict wants not only to advise you of your privacy rights but also explain how we intend to respect them.

Any reference to ?9japredict? or the ?Group? within this Privacy Policy includes 9jaPredict Group and all or any of its direct or indirect subsidiary undertakings, joint venture partners, and their related companies wherever located in the world as may exist from time to time.  
How is your Personal Information collected by our website?   
Personal Information may be submitted on our website in two areas:  
Public Area  
If you do provide your name and address on the public area of this website in order to request information about our products and services, you may voluntarily provide additional personal information. You will be asked to provide your personal information in this area for the purposes of registering with 9jaPredict and opening an account with us. PrivateArea  
If you are already one of our customers and have opened an account with us, you must use a password to enter the Naijapredict website. A "session cookie" is used to enable you to leave and re-enter our website without re-entering your password. Our web server will record the pages you visit within our website. 

To ensure a good quality of service we may monitor and record any communication you have with us whether in writing, by phone or by electronic mail. E-mail is not encrypted to / from either the public or private areas of this website. Betfair recommends that with the exception of your name and username/TAN you do not send us Personal Information by e-mail. Any information which you transmit to us is transmitted at your own risk.

How we use Cookies on our Site and what Information we collect   
For information about cookies please refer to www.allaboutcookies.org  
Session Cookies  
We use session cookies for the following purposes:   
To allow you to carry information across pages of our site and avoid having to re-enter information. Within registration to allow you to access stored information. 

Persistent Cookies  
We use persistent cookies for the following purposes:   
To help us recognise you as a unique visitor when you return to our website and to allow us to tailor content or advertisements to match your preferred interests or to avoid showing you the same adverts repeatedly. To compile anonymous, aggregated statistics that allow us to understand how people use our site and to help us improve the structure of our website. 

To internally identify you by account name, name, email address, customer ID, currency and location (geographic and computer ID/IP address)   
To differentiate users who are on the same network to enable us to correctly allocate bets to the appropriate account. Within research surveys to ensure you are not invited to complete a questionnaire too often or after you have already done so. 

Third Party Cookies  
Third parties serve cookies via this site. These are used for the following purposes:   
To serve advertisements on our site and track whether these advertisements are clicked on by users.   
To control how often you are shown a particular advertisement.   
To tailor content to your preferences.   
To count the number of anonymous users of our site.   
For website usage analysis   
Use of Web Beacons.   
Some of our Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes known as clear gifs) that allow us to count users who have visited these pages. Web beacons collect only limited information which includes a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides. We may also carry web beacons placed by third party advertisers. These beacons do not carry any personally identifiable information and are only used to track the effectiveness of a particular campaign. Disabling/Enabling Cookies.   
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. However, you may not be able to use all the interactive features of our site if cookies are disabled.  
To find out how to enable/disable cookies see www.allaboutcookies.org.

How your Personal Information will be used?   
NaijaPredict will process your Personal Information in order to allow you access and make use of our website, to allow you to participate in the services offered, to administer your account, to maintain our accounts and records, to monitor website usage levels and the quality of the service we provide and to inform you, from time to time, about products and services that we consider may interest you and for related purposes. If you do not wish to receive future marketing, promotional or sales material from NaijaPredict, you may notify us that no further material be sent to you. Our contact details are located in the 'Contact Us' pages of our website. NaijaPredict will as soon as reasonably practicable after receiving your request, remove your contact details from our marketing database.

NaijaPredictt will also retain such information and may analyse it if asked to do so in order to investigate any actual or suspected criminal activity or, in respect of any event featured on our website, any threat to the integrity of that event and/or breaches of the rules of that event as laid down by the relevant governing (including sporting) bodies. All rights in the manner of recording your Personal Information held by NaijaPredict (including copyright and database rights) are and shall remain its property.

Telephone calls and betting data relating to users will be recorded and may be actively monitored for which purposes all users hereby consent.  
To whom and where personal information may be disclosed?   
Your Personal Information may, for the purposes described above, be transferred or disclosed to any company within the Group or, subject to appropriate agreement to third parties, for the processing of that Personal Information on our behalf. The Group may, from time to time, retain third parties to process your Personal Information for the purposes listed above and such processing will be governed by a contract in the form required by law.

Where required by law, your Personal Information may also be disclosed to an applicable governmental, regulatory, sporting or enforcement authority. Additionally, your Personal Information may be disclosed to any regulatory or sporting body in connection with policing the integrity or enforcing the rules of a sport or game and/or prevention and detection of crime and with whom the Group has agreements (Memoranda of Understanding or ?MOUs?) from time to time for the sharing of such data and where the Group considers that there are reasonable grounds to suspect that you may be involved in a breach of such rules or the law, have knowledge of a breach of such rules or the law or otherwise pose a threat to the integrity of the relevant sport or game. Those bodies may then use your Personal Information to investigate and act on any such breaches in accordance with their procedures.

Consent   
By providing your Personal Information and registering with us or logging on with us when you enter our website, you explicitly consent to the Group processing and disclosing your Personal Information for the purposes, and otherwise in the manner, set out in this policy, or as otherwise provided in accordance with the Terms and Conditions. If you wish to qualify, vary, modify or limit your consent in relation to marketing communications or in circumstances where any processing of your data is likely to cause damage or distress or such other circumstances as the law allows then you may do so by notifying us in writing. Our contact details are located in the 'Contact Us' pages of our website.  
NaijaPredict reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy including altering the purposes for which it processes your Personal Information. In the event that Betfair considers it appropriate to make any such change, the Privacy Policy will be updated and posted on our site. Your continued use of the site will constitute acceptance of those changes.  
For full details about Group members, where they operate, or for a copy of your Personal Information or any other queries you may have about our Privacy Policy, please contact us. Again, our contact details are located in the 'Contact Us' pages of our website.
